<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TTJJ</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="tit_home">Home</string>
    <string name="tit_contact_us">Contact us</string>
    <string name="tit_notifications">Notifications</string>
    <string name="tit_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="tit_about_us">About us</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="contact_info_text">\n\n\n Mail Address: \n Nischay J Katariya \n C/o: Jethalal Katariya, \n 11-1-966, \n New NGO\'s Colony, \n Nizamabad, \n Telangana-503002, \n India
        \n \n Call us: \n Nischay Katariya : +91 9949059028 \n Jethalal Katariya : +91 9849059028  \n \nEmail us: \n njkatariya1607@gmail.com
    </string>


    <string-array name="status">
        <item>Up</item>
        <item>Down</item>
        <item>Steady</item>
        <item>Closed</item>

    </string-array>

    <string name="about_us"><b>Introducing TTJJ:</b>\n\n

Nischay J Katariya\n\n

Dear All,\n

I am Nischay J Katariya S/O Jethalal Katariya a Computer Science Engineering

graduate. I joined my father in the year 2013. I welcome you to TTJJ which stands for “Trade

Through Javerchand Jethalal “.\n\n

When I joined him I always wanted to use technology in my business. Finally I came up

with an idea where our firm could be in contact with each and everyone in our clients through an

android application. The application is really very simple. We give you the daily trend of few

commodities like Turmeric, Sesame seeds and cumin seeds from the supplying centers,

weather the trend is up, down or steady when compared to the previous day. This application is

so simple that it can be used by a farmer, trader, exporter or anyone around the world. Based

on these reports that we give, you can decide whether it is the right time to buy any of the above

mentioned commodities. The application will also give you weekly notifications which will

summarize you about the trades and demand in these commodities.\n\n

Our Vision:\n

1. To create experiences where passion and purpose come together.\n

2. To establish TTJJ in the global arena.\n\n

Our Mission:\n

Our mission is to make TTJJ a global enterprise fulfilling its clients’ needs in terms of

quality, quantity and pricing so that it converts its clients into brand advocates.\n\n

Our Strength:\n

1. Competitive pricing\n

2. Quality Products\n

3. On time delivery\n\n

We have always delivered what we promised. We think our clients enjoy working with us

which benefits their business because they believe that we would deliver what has been

promised. We have the experience that a client needs so that the trust and belief gets stronger

every time they work through us.\n\n

So with the above vision, mission and strengths we present you TTJJ.\n\n

Our History\n

Javerchand Jethalal &amp; Co was started on 4 th September 1955 by Late Sri ManjiBhai Katariya.

He was a classic first generation entrepreneur. He was a man who started small, dreamt big

and used a combination of grit and perseverance to create this company.\n

He had a difficult journey in the beginning but he believed that this would create wonders some

day. He tried to keep his business to a manageable size so that he never lost sight of the

relationships that he had built over the years.\n

The success of this company would not be possible if we do not mention Jethalal Katariya who

was the working force behind this company.

Jethalal Katariya’s photo\n

Jethalal Katariya was very keen in joining his father in his business at a very young age. He

joined his father in the year 1969. Following his father’s principles he took the business to new

heights. Breaking all the barriers, he expanded the company’s operations to major parts of the

country.\n\n

Because of Jethalal Katariyas ill health he could not continue trading but he started broking firm

with his son in an improvised name i.e. TTJJ.</string>
</resources>
